《铁血战士》
别开枪
Don't!
- 冷静点 - 去死
- Calm down. - Hey, fuck you!
- Calm down. - Fuck you!
他的降落伞好像没打开
It's like his chute didn't open.
- 一个枪手 - 你怎么知道
- Single shooter! - How do you know?
请别再开枪了
Please, stop doing that!
你打错对象了
You're shooting at the wrong people.
何以见得
How do I know?
如若不是 你早没命了
Because otherwise, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
好吧
Alright.
你想跟我说谁才是该杀的吗
You want to show me the right ones?
尼古拉 我叫尼古拉
Nikolai. I mean...I'm Nikolai.
尼古拉 你最后记得事是什么
What's the last thing you remember, Nikolai?
在打战
War. Yeah.
当时我在车臣
I was at the Chechnya.
然后看到一道光
And then there was a light.
然后我...
Then I...
然后我醒来...
Then I woke up and I was...
自己正降落
Falling.
一样 我当时在包姚
Yeah, same thing. I was in Baja.
看到一道光 然后就到了这鬼地方
And then, there was a light. And then, "chinga"!
我们现在在哪儿
Where are we now?
她可能知道
Maybe she knows.
操
Shit.
可以放下武器吗
You want to lower the weapon?
我从未来过这个丛林 但曾看过很多次
I've never seen this jungle. And I've seen most.
好吧 你觉得是在亚洲? 或者非洲?
Alright. You think that's Asia? Maybe Africa?
对于这个季节来说 天气过热了
Too hot for this time of year.
还有地势全错的
And the topography is all wrong.
可能是 亚马逊
Amazon, maybe.
我见到了很多降落伞
I saw more parachutes.
- 哪条路 - 干吗
- Which way? - Why?
这样我才能知道谁他妈的把我扔出了飞机
So I can figure out who threw me out of a fucking airplane.
我操 她要去哪儿
What the fuck? Where she goes?
瞎扯淡 如果我们听这个...
Bullshit, if we listen to this...
好吧 我们就他妈的去看看吧
Alright, let's take a fucking look.
我操
Fuck.
你记得飞机吗
Do you remember a plane?
我在降落途中醒的 你呢
I woke up in free fall. You?
一样
The same.
你是以色列国防军?
You're IDF?
是的 你在那里服过役?
Yeah. You've been in the service?
不完全是
Not exactly.
混蛋
Motherfucker!
滚开 操蛋的
Move you motherfucker!
- 你跟他一伙的吗 - 不是
- You with him? - No.
那你他妈的少管闲事
Then why don't you mind your own fucking business?
我们现在有更棘手的问题
We have bigger problems right now.
好吧 头儿 都听你的
Okay, boss. Whatever you say.
我会给你善终的
I will finish what you started.
人多势众啊
Strength in numbers, huh?
- 算是吧 - 是的...
- Stuff like that. - Yeah...
也许我们该把挂在树上的那家伙弄下来
Maybe we should get that guy hanging in the tree.
救我 我操
Help me! Fuck!
救我 来人啊
Help me! Somebody!
救我
Help!
有人吗
Hello?
我他妈的被降落伞捆在树上了
I'm strapped in a parachute in a fucking tree!
- 你他妈的干吗不闭上你的臭嘴 - 谢天谢地
- Why don't you shut the fuck up? - Oh, thank God!
我想我可以...
I think I can...
别挣扎了 树枝快被你折断了
Stop moving, you are breaking the branch.
你身上有东西可以把降落伞割断吗
Do you have anything to cut yourself down with?
为什么... 没 没有
Why would it... No, I dont.
如果我们可以使他挣脱其中一个降落伞斜槽
Look. If we can get him broke from one of the chute.
做点什么啊
Do something!
- 救我 - 多省事啊
- Help! - Taking too long.
救我
Help!
- 你到底是谁 - 我是个医生...
- Who the hell are you? - I'm a doctor...
我在去上班的途中
I was on my way to work.
有人能告诉我...
Can someone please just tell me...
这到底是怎么回事吗
What the fuck is going on here?
你的屁股真性感
Your ass is awesome.
看
Look.
见鬼 这家伙到底是谁啊
Hot damn! Who the hell is this guy?
那到底是什么东西
What the hell is that?
谁弄的啊
Who would do this?
不管是谁弄的 他们会得到战利品
Whoever they are, they take trophies.
在我们国家 勇士拥有最大的战利品...
In my culture, the warrior with the greatest trophies...
- 将受到至高无上的敬仰 - 管它呢
- Command the most respect. - Whatever.
这是一次测试
It's a test.
看我们在压力之下会怎么做
To see how we do under pressure.
如果这是个测试 那你们就都是军人了
If this were a test, you'd all be military.
完全陌生的人 带着真枪实弹
Total strangers, live rounds.
一定是别的什么
This is something else.
也许是绑架通缉令 回归提加纳(墨西哥西北部城市)
Maybe it's ransom. Back in Tijuana,
我们绑架你 并把你放进油桶里
We kidnap you, put you in an oil drum.
如果不付赎金的话...
If the ransom not paid...
我们就会烧死你
we light you on fire.
我听过这些
I hear these stories,
关于这些试验的故事 都是骗人的
about these experiments they roll on cons.
他们把药放进你的食物
They stick drugs in your food,
然后待在一边 观察会发生什么事
and sit back and watch what happens.
不是药
It's not drugs.
如果是精神治疗药物化合物的话...
If there was a psychotropic compound,
我们会受到残留药物影响...
we'd be feeling the residual side effects,
散失运动技能 视线模糊...
loss of motor skills, blurry vision...
如果是一种行为学实验的话
And if it was a behavioral experiment, I mean, there'd...
会有一个目标
be a point.
如果我们死了怎么办
What if we are dead.
- 我本来在两天内要被处决 - 我本来在打仗
- I was gonna be executed in two days. - And I was in combat.
我也是
So was I.
这是地狱
This is hell.
上次我看到你不需要降落伞就到达那里
Last time I looked you didn't need a parachute to get there.
但不管发生了什么事 或是为什么
But it doesn't matter what happened, or why.
我们现在...
We're here...
唯一的问题就是...
the only question is...
我们怎么走出去
How do we get out?
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
- 去高地 - 我们不能走散
- To high ground. - We need to stick together.
那你们就该跟着我走
Then you should follow me.
不要碰它
Yeah, I wouldn't do that.
辽宁古果
Archaefructus liaoningensis.
含有剧毒
That is really, really poisonous.
轻轻一碰 就会导致全身麻痹
Wouldn't take more than one scratch, cause total paralysis.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会保护你离开这里
I will watch for you out here.
你交了个兄弟啊
You made a buddy.
我们得休息一下
We need to rest.
那就休息啊
So rest.
你看起来也累了
You look like you could use it too.
你叫什么
You got a name?
听着...
Look...
抱歉 你想要做童子军小队长? 很好
I'm sorry. You want to play scout leader? Great.
现在你要跟着我? 行
Now you gonna follow me? Fine.
我可不会做这个...
But I'm not doing this...
我还是独自一人的好
I'm better on my own.
想要看真格的吗
Want to see something fucked up?
在那个和太阳之间...
Well, between that and the sun...
- 我们真的有问题了 - 那太阳呢
- I'd say we have a real problem. - What about the sun?
自从我们到了这儿 就没见太阳动过
It hasn't moved since we got here.
你觉得到底会发生什么事
What do you think is really going on?
我怎么想
What do I think?
反恐特种部队
Spetznatz alpha group,
洛泽塔斯(墨西哥最大的犯罪集团) 联合企业杀手
Los Zetas cartel enforcer,
革命联合阵线 来自塞拉利昂的行刑队
R.U.F. that's a death squad from Sierra Leone,
杀手山口组
Yakuza in the Dawokei,
美国联邦调查局最想要的
the F.B.I.'s most wanted,
还有...他
and him.
他们都是重量级人物 他不属于...
They're all heavy-hitters, he doesn't belong.
不属于什么
Belong to what?
我要说的是我们被选中了
Well, I'd say we were chosen.
那你呢
What about you?
我?
What about me?
你知道丛林 所有选手...
You know the jungle, all the players...
我猜你以前是军队的 从事机密工作
I'm guessing ex-military, black-ops,
- 可能是个雇佣兵 - 你对此有问题吗
- Probably a mercenary. - You got a problem with that?
此刻没有
Not at the moment.
很好
Good.
有什么东西曾降落到这里
Something was dropped here.
跟我们一样
Same as us.
跟我们不一样
Not the same as us.
你说过我们是被选中的
You said we were chosen.
被选中干吗
Chosen for what?
我操
Oh, shit.
走路小心点 头儿
Looking good there, boss.
小心 快闪开
Look out! Step!
救命
Help!
- 12点钟方向 110米处 - 搞定他...
- 12 o'clock. 110 meters. - Take him! Take him!
不用了
We don't have to.
他死了
He left.
我们触发了一个死人设的机关
We triggered a dead man's trap.
从腐烂程度判断
It's two weeks.
已经死亡两个礼拜了
Judging from the rate of decomposition.
他占据适当位置
He took up a position here.
这里可以扫射所有方向
Shooting in all directions.
这是最后抵抗
This was a last stand.
美国特种兵
United States special forces.
奇怪了
This is strange.
他本该被部署于阿富汗
He's supposed to be deployed in Afghanistan.
他怎么会在这里给我们设机关
What's he doing here setting traps for us?
这些不是针对我们的
They weren't meant for us.
他在追捕其它什么东西...
He was hunting something else...
- 某些更大的东西 - 更大?
- Something a lot bigger. - Bigger?
树干是一种陷阱
The trunk was a dead-fall.
概测法加上陷阱
The rule of thumb with a dead-fall,
就是你设定的目标动物翻5倍重量
is that you set the weight five times that of the target animal.
不管它是什么 它进入陷阱触发绊线
Whatever it was, it got through the trip-wires.
就会一触即发
And did this.
走吧
Let's move.
是什么
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
是什么 没什么
What is it? Nothing.
我们要订个新计划
We're gonna need a new plan.
我们要去哪儿
Hey, where are we going?
既然进得来 就一定出得去
Someone put us on this rock, there's gotta be a way off it.
我操
Ah! What the fuck?
操蛋的小匕首
Hey, you know what? Fuck this!
这个狗屁小匕首 伙计 我要枪
This is bullshit, man. I want a gun!
老兄 快给我 你他妈的有两把枪啊
Come man. You got two mother fucking guns, man!
有人给我一把枪吧
Somebody give me a gun!
快给我啊 俄国佬 你他妈的有把大枪
Come on Russian, you got a big fucking gun!
快点 老兄 给我把枪
Come on man, give me a gun.
给我把枪 马上
Give me a gun, right now!
给我把枪
Give me a gun.
我早已做好死亡准备了
I'm ready to die.
你呢
Are you?
救命
Help!
我操
Fuck you!
小心点 头儿
Looking good there, boss.
快跑...快爬上去
Run! Run! Come on! Climb!
操你妈的
Oh, shit!
不要啊
No!
跟你一样坏...
As bad as you are...
那些东西更糟糕
those things are worse.
既然我们一个没少 它们刚...怎么 离开了?
Since we still eight, they just...what? Left?
不是
No.
是哨音
The whistle.
它们被召唤回去了
They were called.
好了 听着
Alright. Listen up!
大家数一下子弹
Everybody do a shell count.
我们要保存弹药
We've got to conserve ammunition.
重新装入弹药 马上装
Reload. Do it now.
抱歉 这到底是怎么回事
Excuse me, I'm...just what the hell is going on here?
我们正在被追捕
We're being hunted.
笼子 士兵 我们所有人
The cages, soldier, all of us.
都是因同一个目的被带到这儿
All brought here for the same purpose.
这个星球是个野生动物保护区
This planet is a game preserve.
而我们就是那些野生动物
And we're the game.
以防万一你没注意到
In case you didn't notice,
我们刚就被驱赶出来
we just got flushed out.
他们放狗进来
They sent the dogs in.
就像如果你在追踪野猪
Just like you would if you were stalking boar.
开枪以示警告
Shooting quail.
他们把我们分开 然后暗中观看
They split us apart, and they watched.
测试我们
Testing us.
你怎么知道所有事的
How do you know all this?
因为...
Because...
那就是我以前所作的事
that's what I would do.
- 妙极了 - 等等...
- Fantastic. - Wait...
- 我们只有7个人 - 救我
- There are only seven of us. - Help me!
救命
Help!
Help.
- 等等... - 怎么了
- Wait... - What?
是个陷阱
It's a trap.
救我
Help me.
我操
Fuck me.
救命
Help.
使一个人受伤
Wound one man.
使他受罪
Make him suffer.
使他流血
Make him bleed.
使他发出呼救
Make him call out for help.
然后设陷阱 杀死来救他的人
And set a trap, and kill those who come.
我知道 因为我曾干过这事
I know, because I have done this.
那我们要把他留在这儿 对吗
So we're gonna leave him here, right?
得了吧 看看他 他已经玩完了
Come on, look at him. He's done.
我们没别的可做的了 对吗
There's nothing...there's nothing else we can do, right?
对吗
Right?
别管他
We leave him.
不行
I can't.
那你来解决吧
Then that's on you.
救我
Help me.
救我 救我 是个陷阱 是个陷阱
Help me. Help me. It's a trap. It's a trap.
我们要做什么
What are we gonna do?
我们该去更高处
We should go to higher ground.
是吗
Really?
我们被困在一个外星人的捕猎星球
We're trapped on an alien hunting planet,
你真的认为解决的办法是...
you really think the solution is to...
行走?
walk over?
它想我们跑
It wants us to run.
这才是猎捕的意义
That's how it hunts.
这是它的丛林
This is its jungle.
它的游戏
Its game.
它的规则
Its rules.
我们跑...
We run...
我们死
we die.
没有别的选择了吗
What's the alternative?
我们要知道我们在对付的是什么
We need to know what we're dealing with.
狗朝这个方向跑的
The dog tracks go that way.
我们跟着它走
We go after it.
怎么了
What?
没有动静
No movement.
看来 我们并不是唯一被追捕的东西
Looks like, we're not the only things been hunted.
妈的
Oh, shit!
那他妈是什么东西
What the fuck is that thing?
这是个错误 我们必须离开 马上
This is a mistake.We have to leave. Now!
那个硬汉哪儿去了
Where's the tough guy?
他离开我们了
He left us.
他在这儿
He's here.
跑
Run!
跑 跑
Run! Run!
跑 跑 跑
Run! Run! Run!
你设计我们
You set us up!
他让我们进那个死亡集中营的
He led us into that death camp.
然后藏起来等着那个东西来袭击
Then hid and waited for that thing to strike.
我们是诱饵
We were bait.
我得知道我们在对付的是什么
I needed to know who we're up against.
- 现在我来 - 有个人就因此而死了
- Now I do. - A man is dead because of that.
今天早上你就准备杀了他的
This morning you were ready to kill him.
这他妈跟今天早晨没关系
Well it ain't this god damn morning, is it?
- 至少他不是白死的 - 为什么
- Well at least he didn't die in vain. - Why?
好让我们可以第一时间发现
So we could find out first-hand,
那种我们被人扁的感觉怎么样
what it feels like to have our asses kicked?
不 我们发现它们不止一个
No, we found out that there's more than one of them,
他们用的是自动推进式武器和能量武器
that they use projectile and energy based weapons,
他们有某种隐形装置
that they have some sort of cloaking device,
他们比我们大
that they're bigger than us,
比我们结实
stronger.
也比我们沉
But also heavier.
你为了自己拿我们去冒险
You've put us at risk for yourself.
你想要孤军奋战吗
Do you wanna be in your own?
可以
You got it.
你为什么不跟他们说实话呢
Why don't you tell them the true?
- 我不知道你在说什么... - 你很清楚我在说什么
- I don't know what you're talking... - You know what I'm talking about.
你看那个东西的眼神格外紧张
The way you looked to that thing, that was strung up.
你的反应
The way you reacted.
她知道那是什么
She knows what it is.
不是吗
Don't you.
我们没有名字来称呼他们
We don't have a name for them.
危地马拉87
'87, Guatemala.
一支特种部队进入了丛林
A Spec ops team went into the jungle.
高端得很
High end.
六个人外加一个中情局联络员
Six men plus a CIA liaison.
只有一个成功了
Only one made it out.
在他的报告中
In his debrief...
他说他们接触到了某样东西
he said they came in contact with something.
他做了详细描述
He gave a detailed description.
图腾上的东西
The thing on the totem.
那东西穿了什么伪装以此来适应背景光线
It wore some kind of camouflage that adjusted to ambient light.
会使它在我们的光谱仪上近似隐形
Made it nearly invisible in our spectrum.
在红外线下可以看见它
It could see in infra red.
高温特征
Heat signatures.
他用泥来阻挡 这是他打击它的方法
He used mud to block his. That's how he beat it.
那东西追捕着 然后杀害他的队伍
It hunted, and killed his team.
一个接一个
One by one.
不管它是什么
Whatever it is.
不管它们从哪儿来
Wherever they're from.
我们要把它们杀光
We gonna kill 'em all.
我们设一个防御周界
We set up a defensive perimeter.
让它觉得我们滞留在这里 让它们来找我们
Make it look like we're holding up. And that will bring 'em to us.
我们逼它们陷入瓶颈 让它们进入射程
We force them into a choke point. We get 'em in overlap in fields of fire.
可以做到
It can be done.
我一个人不行
I can't do it alone.
伙计 如果我们是在家
You know man, if we ever make it home...
我他妈要弄很多的可卡因
I'm going to do so much fucking cocaine.
我要把那些小婊子强奸个够
I'm gonna rape so many fine bitches.
几点了 5点了? 妈的
About, what time is it? 5 o'clock? Damn.
强奸婊子的时候到了
Time to go rape me some fine bitches.
你知道我在说什么吗
You know what I'm saying?
当然 完全清楚
Oh yeah, totally.
大概...5点钟
It's like, 5 o'clock...
- 强奸婊子的时间 - 是
- Bitch raping time. - Hmm, yeah.
- 你该离他远点 - 是啊
- You should stay away from him. - Yeah.
你还生气呢
You still pissed?
操
Fuck you.
你知道我们俩的区别是什么吗
You know, what the difference between you and me is.
我们都是在做同样的事
We both did the same thing.
你是为你的国家而做 所以你不用承认你喜欢它
You just do it for your country so you don't have to admit you like it.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
什么事把你弄成这样
What made you so fucked up?
没有这样猎捕的
There is no hunting like the hunting of a man.
那些长时间猎捕有武装的
And those who have hunted armed men long enough,
并且喜欢上此行为的人
and liked it,
从不真正关心以后的事情
never really care for anything else thereafter.
真是诗情画意啊
That's pretty poetic.
全是你自己想出来的?
Did you come up with that all by yourself?
其实不是
No, actually.
是海明威
That was Hemingway.
那东西他妈的在哪儿呢
Where the fuck is it?
为什么不过来呢
Why isn't it coming?
让我看看你的陷阱
Let me see your traps.
- 你好 医生 - 你好
- Hey, Doc. - Hey.
我刚刚想出了让你有用的办法
I think I just figured out a way you can be useful.
操
Shit!...
我在左边 只有我听到了信号
I'm in left side, just I heard the sign!
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on!
- 妈的 - 快点 快点
- Oh, shit! - Come on, come on.
快他妈射啊
Fucking shoot!
已经在打了
Shoot it already!
我操
Fuck...
你们所有人
all of you!
他死了吗 你为什么不笑了
Is he dead? Why ain't you smiling?
- 妈的 - 那东西是从笼子里出来的
- Oh, shit. - The thing from the cages.
可能他想着我们准备来这儿呢
Maybe he thought we were going to draw up till here.
不管怎么说 打得好
Good shot, though.
我打偏了
I missed.
在这儿呢
Over here.
这边
你到底他妈是什么
What the fuck are you?
我是活人
I'm alive.
你说话太大声了
You talk too loud.
你一来这儿我就闻见了
I've smelled you since you got here.
如果我能闻到你 如果我能听见你
If I can smell you, if I can hear you...
它们也可以
They can too.
暴风雨马上要来了 这边走
Storm coming soon, this way.
等一下
Wait.
你是谁
Who are you?
诺兰逃跑了
Noland run away.
留着等改天再战
Live to fight another day.
我是逃跑的那个
I'm the one that got away.
你没有打着的那个
The one you don't fuck with.
得了吧 这地方满是恐惧
Come on, fear revive in this place.
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
有人落下了一本日记
There's a journal somebody left behind.
那个机器死了 但是能源还在
The machine's dead. The power source, ain't.
看看这洞 你住这儿吗
Wow, what a shit hole. You live here?
不 不 这是我夏天的度假屋
Oh, no, no. This is my summer home.
我冬天住里维埃拉
I winter in the Riviera.
那儿的学校比这儿好得多
The schools are so much nicer there.
那儿的人 哎呀呀...
And the men? Ooh la la...
顺道说一句 不客气
By the way, you're welcome.
你是怎么活下来的
How have you survived?
所有能用的废物都用上
Salvaging what I can,
尽最大的可能
when I can, from whatever I can.
诺兰 罗纳德 "空气制造器"
Noland, Ronald. "Air Cav".
他们...
They...
他们把你们也扯进来了?
they drop you all in too?
是的
Yeah.
怎么这么急
What a rush?
我会告诉他的
Hey...yeah, I'll tell him.
"落叶剂" 你想要...
Hey "Agent Orange", you wanna...
放下
put that down.
这里的有些人过分挑剔别人
Several people around here particular about other people messing with their shit.
虽然非常重要
Very important, though.
扰乱高温信号
Disrupts the heat signature.
操你妈的
You motherfuckers!
所以你杀了一个?
So you killed one?
堆 我杀了一个 两个...
Aha, I killed one. Two...
可能是三个 我记不起来了
Maybe three. No, I can't remember.
不管怎么说 它们...
Anyway, there's...
它们有两种不同的类型
two different types of them out there.
现在 他们很相似 但是有区别
Now, they're similar, but they're different.
有点像狼和狗的区别
It's kinda like, the difference between dogs and wolves.
但是有一个会一直跑到这儿
But the ones it'll running things up there...
大一点的会狩猎小一点的
the larger ones hunt the smaller ones.
有点像...
It's some kind of...
我想是血海深仇 已经很久了
blood-feud I guess, that's been going on for a long time.
是吗
Oh, yeah.
- 它们做这个只是为了运动? - 是的
- And they do this, just for sport? - Oh, yeah...
它们带来新鲜的肉 一季又一季
And they bringing in fresh meat, season after season...
你他妈是不会相信的
I mean, shit you wouldn't believe.
带进来...
Bring it in...
然后...
and...
打猎 然后杀了它
hunt it, and kill it. In that order.
你在这儿多久了 伙计
How long have you been here, man?
7个季节了吧 我想...
Seven seasons, I think...
什么
What?
10个? 该死...
Ten? Damn...
不管怎么说 过一阵一次
Anyway. Every once in a while,
我们中的一个杀掉它们中的一个...
one of us kills one of them...
让我来告诉你 它们什么时候真的感兴趣
and let me tell you, that's when they get real interested.
你看 它们学习...
See, they learn...
灵敏 它们适应
quick, they adapt.
它们发展出一种全新的技能
They develop a whole new set of skills.
它们下个季节回来 成群的 总是成群的
They come back the next season. In threes, always in threes.
它们的盔甲可能有所改变了
Their armor might have changed.
或者它们武器变了 或者...
Or their weapons have changed, or...
它们的策略变了
their tactics have changed.
太神奇了
It's amazing.
所以 就像是进化一样
So, it's like an evolution...
它们通过训练来使自己变成更好的杀手
They train to make themselves in to better killers.
你说过 它们回来...
You said, they come back...
怎样回来
How?
- 它们有船 - 船?
- They got a ship. - A ship?
是的 离它们的营地30码
Yeah. It's 30 yards from their camp.
我告诉过你 它们看不见它
I told you they wouldn't see it.
我告诉过你 它们看不见
I told you they wouldn't.
你去过那儿
You were there.
你应该帮帮我们
You could've helped us.
我们怎么杀它们
How do we kill them?
不管怎么说你可以
However you can.
它们一定有弱点
They must have a weakness.
不是很多
Not many.
你想要活命?
You wanna survive?
你得挖个深点的洞藏起来
You'd dig in deep, you stay hid.
是 我们从二号门走
Yeah, well we're gonna go with door number two.
我们怎样走出这个山谷?
How do we get out of this valley?
10个季节...
Ten seasons...
第一第二个季节 不 三季我都在这儿
The first two seasons. No, three seasons I was here,
我当时顺着同一个方向走
I was walking in the same direction.
试着接近保护区的边界
Trying to reach the edge of the preserve.
让我来告诉你吧 根本没有什么"保护区的边界"
Let me tell you something, there ain't no "edge of the preserve".
也许你 或者你的朋友想跟我谈谈那艘船
Maybe you or your friend wanna tell me about that ship.
我明白了...
I see...
那是...
That's...
绝妙的主意 太妙了
a brilliant idea. Brilliant.
所有的时间我都待在这儿 它从没出现过...
The whole time I've been here, it never occurred to me to...
霸占外星人航天器
commandeer the alien spacecraft.
但是我不知道那玩意怎么飞
But I wouldn't know how to fly it.
他会的
He would.
因为你知道怎么开那玩意?
Because you know how to fly it?
我会试试的
I'll give it a shot.
那...
Well...
我要去睡一会儿了
I'm gonna get some sleep.
别出声 它们在外面
No noise, they're out there.
它们总是在外面
They're always out there.
水在那里面
The water in there.
大家自便吧
Help yourself, all of you.
那是谁
Who's that?
我的孩子
My kids.
大一点的是瑞恩 还有萨沙
The big one is Rien, and Sasha.
这是蜜糖·李
This is...Candy Lee.
咪咪像榴弹炮
Tits like Howitzers.
那是你女朋友吗
Is that your girlfriend?
不 那是我妹妹
No, it's my sister.
这个很老 非常老
This is old. Very old.
它们做这个已经很久了
They've been doing this for a long time.
你会说英语
You speak English.
是的
Yes.
为什么不多说点
Why don't you say more?
正因为我说得太多了
Because I talk too much.
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道我被带走的时候在干什么吗
Do you know what I was doing when I was taken?
以撒 我的观察员
Isaac, my spotter.
他被抓了
He was caught.
我什么都做不了
I could've done something,
但随后我会和他一样被杀掉
but then I would've been slaughtered along with him.
所以我藏起来了
So I hid.
我看着他死去
I watched him die.
我希望我扣了扳机
I wish I pulled that trigger.
你在做的是你必须做的事 生存
You're doing what you have to do, to survive.
你说过我们是被选中的
You said we were chosen.
我要求什么了
I asked for what.
我不能问为什么
I should've asked why.
那是因为我们...
It's because we...
是铁血战士
are predators.
就像它们一样
Just like them.
我们是我们自己世界里的野兽
We're the monsters, of our own world.
唯一一点好处就是我们从不回去
It's only better, that we're never going back.
不 我要回去
No, I'm going back.
我要跟着那艘船
I'm going after that ship.
你指望着最后还能飞
You're gonna hope to fly it in the last hour,
然后现在才告诉我?
and now you tell me?
不
No.
那东西现在已经在营地里紧张不安了
That thing strung up in the camp right now.
据我推测 它会为了自由不惜一切的
In my guess, it'd do just about anything to get free.
敌人的敌人
Enemy of my enemy.
也不能成为朋友
It doesn't make it a friend.
我该怎么称呼你
So, what do I call you?
烟
Smoke!
Hey! Smoke!
诺兰在哪儿
Where's Noland?
他是个清道夫 他想要我们的东西
He's a scavenger. He wants what we have.
拜托 一定有路可以出去的
Come on, there must be away out.
- 该死 - 就这么做 我们快离开这里
- Damn it! - Do it! Let's get out of here!
看见你把我们害成什么样子 伙计
You see the shit you got us into, man?
我跟你说什么来着
I told you that,
你们永远都不听我的
you'd never listening to me, you know.
6张 要他妈养活6张嘴
Six more, six more fucking mouths to feed.
我几乎忍受不了跟你们生活
I can barely stand live with you!
我想和他们的食物一起生活
I wanna live with their food!
该死
Damn it!
怎么了
What?
跟你的小朋友说再见吧
Say goodbye to your little friend!
你是在我的房子里 混蛋
You're in my house motherfucker!
趴下
Get down!
是啊 那他妈没打开
Yeah, that didn't open up shit!
不会的 混蛋
It wasn't meant to, asshole.
我正在叫装甲部队呢
I'm calling in the cavalry.
他妈让我出去
Let's fucking get out!
开门 快点 操
Open up! Do it, fucker!
快点
Come on!
你终于找到我了 大狗
You finally found me ha, big dog?
那...
Well...
是什么耽误了你这么久
What took you so long?
根本打不开
It's not gonna open! Come on!
该死的
God damn it!...
它在玩我们呢
It's toying with us.
伙计们 妈的
Guys! Oh, shit!
来 这边
Come on. This way.
我...我...我跟丢了
I, I...I lost you guys.
拜托
Come on.
你们得把我从这儿弄出去啊 伙计 快点
You've got to get me out of here, man. Come on.
我们走
Let's move.
瞧瞧你这张脸
What a face you got on you!
我们杀了它
We killed it!
我们杀了它 我们他妈...
We killed it! We fuckin'...
我们他妈杀了它
We fuckin' killed it!
我们杀了它
We killed it!
我们他妈杀了它
We fuckin' killed it!
现在知道谁厉害了吧 操你妈的
Huh? Who's your Daddy now, motherfucker?
现在知道谁厉害了吧 操你妈
来舔我啊 婊子
Suck my dick, bitch!
死你的吧 笨蛋
Die you space faggot!
你想你在跟谁玩呢
Who do you think you're dealing with, huh?
你就这么点本事吗 走啊 走啊
Is that all you got? Go! Go! Go!
来啊 来啊 来啊
Come on...come on! Come on!
来啊 来啊
Come on! Come on!
我们去弄那艘船去
Let's get to that ship.
妈的
Oh, shit!
Ah, shit!
妈的 操
Shit! Fuck!
一个不同大小 它会伤到我的胫骨动脉的
A nother inch. It would hit my tibial artery.
- 我想今天是我的幸运日吧 - 才不是
- I guess it's my lucky day. - It isn't.
那个陷阱不是想杀了我们
That trap wasn't meant to kill.
它的目的是为了弄伤猎物
It was meant to maim.
他该死的重量 来
He's dead weight. Come on.
不 我能...我还能走
No, I can...I can still walk.
操 天啊
Oh, shit! God!
不 我们不能带着他 他已经完了
No, we can't let him through. He's done.
你会求着我们慢下来的
You gonna beg us to slow down,
- 不 不 不... - 来抬着你
- No, no, no.... - to carry you.
你们不能把我留在这儿
You can't leave me here.
你不能 我有家
You can't. I have a family.
我有...我有孩子
I've...I got kids.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 我们必须得走了 - 不 不
- We need to go. - No, no!
你会带着我一起的 你会带着我一起的
You're taking me with you! You're taking me with you!
操你 我还能行
Fuck you, I can still make it.
我们用他
We use him.
我们拿他做陷阱
We booby trap him.
- 不... - 它们会把他当战利品的
- No... - They'll go to him to take trophies.
这是我们最后的机会
This is our last chance.
不行 他是我们的一员
This isn't right, he's one of us.
他是 它们就是这么打算的
He is. That's what they're counting on.
它们想要你从这人身上感觉到一些东西
They want you to feel something for this man,
成为人类
to be human.
那你是什么
And what are you?
活的
Alive.
那有什么值得的
What's that worth?
求你了 求你了 我求求你 拜托
Please. Please, I'm begging you. Please.
你该走了
You should go.
- 来 - 好的
- Come on. - Okey.
- 你不该带他走的 - 我知道
- You should've gone with him. - I know.
我想要离开这个星球
I want off this planet.
你明白我的意思吗
You understand me?
我会放了你
I'll cut you down.
你带我去那艘船
You take me to the ship.
船
The ship.
你明白我的意思 对吗
You understand me, don't you?
操
Shit!
- 天啊 - 对不起
- God.  - I'm sorry.
我们还没死呢
Well, we're not dead yet.
操
Shit!
我想他做到了
I guess he made it.
如果我们能再来一遍的话
If we can do it over again,
你还会做一样的选择吗
would you make the same choice?
是的
Yes.
谢谢你
Thank you.
如果时光重来的话
When the time comes,
我会两者都选
I'll choose both.
我跟你保证会很快
I promise you it will be quick.
不...
No...
不会的
It won't.
对了
That's right.
它是一种神经毒素
It's a neurotoxin.
我们在这儿面临这么多选择
So many to choose from around here.
但是别担心 它不会致命的
But don't worry. It's not fatal.
你只是体验一下...
You'll be able to experience...
所有事物
everything.
我想现在你知道 他们为什么选择我了吧
I guess now you realize why they chose me.
我的时间永远都在你们之前
I was in front of you guys the whole time.
看着你们
Watching you.
聆听你们的信仰
Earning your trust.
你看不到真实的我是什么样子
You couldn't see me for what I really am.
你看 回到家里..
You see, back home...
我是个杀人犯
I'm a murderer.
我是个变态
I'm a freak.
但是在这儿
But here,
所有的怪物聚在一起...
among the monsters...
我就是个正常人
I'm normal.
我喜欢在这的感觉
I like it here.
我想留下来
I want to stay.
你回来了
Oh, you came back.
我错过了那班车
I missed my ride.
谢天谢地 快帮我们从这儿出去
Oh, thank God. Help us get out of here.
她瘫痪了
She's paralyzed.
可能它们给了她什么东西 我不知道
Maybe they gave her something, I don't know what.
但是让她瘫痪了
But it paralyzed her.
来吧
Come on.
你太忙了 都没怎么在意
You're so busy, you didn't care about it.
你要照顾好你自己
You've got to look out for yourself.
我们要从这儿出去了 抓紧了
We're getting out of here, just stay in tight.
现在我不觉得你会回来了
Now, I didn't think you'd come back.
但是她...
But she...
她从来没有不相信你
she never lost faith on you.
我想我欠你一个道歉
I guess I owe you an apology.
你终究是个好人
You are a good man after all.
不...
No...
我不是
I'm not.
但是我很快就是了
But I'm fast.
来
Come here.
求你了 不要杀我 求你 不要杀我
Please, don't kill me! Please, don't kill me!
我不会的
I won't!
救命啊
Help me.
我是你们的一员
I'm one of you.
快点 快点 下手啊
Come on, come on! Do it!
这儿呢 杀了我 快点
Over here, kill me! Come on!
快点 现在就下手 杀了我
Come on! Do it now! Kill me!
妈的
Oh, shit!
你杀了它吗
Did you kill it?
是的
Yeah.
我是罗伊斯
I'm Royce.
很高兴见到你 罗伊斯
Nice to meet you, Royce.
我是伊莎贝尔
I'm Isabelle.
现在...
Now...
让我们想个办法离开这鬼地方
Let's find a way off this fucking planet.